I'm sorry.
ごめんなさい
Ah yes, this classic scene. It's just like they always say:
昔からこういう場面でよく使う言葉をあなたに贈るわ
If "sorry" was enough, then we wouldn't need the police, would we?
ごめんで済んだら 警察はいらないんじゃない
And after all that fuss, you let Talisman,
the very man you were after, slip through your fingers.
あれだけ大騒ぎしておいて結局 本命のタリスマンは逃亡
I never should have cooperated with the police in the first place.
本当に警察なんかと手を組むんじゃなかった
But there's no doubt that Talisman has gotten caught up in some sort of crime.
でもね　タリスマンが犯罪に巻き込まれているのは間違いないの
You helped us because you felt you couldn't just ignore that, right?
あなただってそれを見過ごせないと思ったから手伝ってくれたんでしょ
Give me a break!
いいかげんにして 私はスプーキーブーギー·ザ·アナーキー
I'm Spooky Boogie, the anarchist!
Under no circumstances will I ever act as your agent again.
もうどんなことがあろうと　金輪際 あなたたちの手先にはならないわ
But...
そんな…
Bad news for your friendship?
友情にヒビ入れちゃったかしら
Well, she was just someone who used to be in my class.
でも　そもそも同級生ってだけで 誰なのかまでは分からないし
I don't even know who she is, really.
You recorded that chat, right?
今のチャットはログを取ってあるな
What?
Yeah, of course.
えっ　そりゃもちろん
Dare ni mo miserarenai mono
My head is full of things
Atama no naka afurete
That I can never tell anybody of
In this perfect world
Machigai sae mo nai sekai he
I roam, a lost being
Mayoikonderu
Arienai hodo surikomareteru
This world is impossibly hard on me
It's an illusion that plays out before my eyes
Me ni mieru mono dake no "sekai" genshou
Abakidaseru kana
Can I find its faults?
Plastic tac tic
Plastic, all is plastic
Mou dare mo okashiku narenai yo
Nobody is allowed to be insane
Kisama mo plastic beautiful world
You're made of plastic too, like this beautiful world
In this beautiful world
Utsukushi sugiru sekai ni
Boku wa nazeka
There is something
Hikari ga mienakute
That obscures all light for me
Haretsu shite yuku kokoro ga
My heart tries to break out
And finds no answer
Mugen no rifurekushon
Secret kills for you
Secret remains for you
The secret remains for you
Don't show me a dark future
Misekake no iro to
Mirai wo abakanai de
Nor a world of pretense
Keep it secret motion
Keep our motion secret
05: Nobody Knows Your Face
Talisman Saloon is packed with guests, as usual.
本字幕由诸神字幕组制作 更多字幕欢迎访问http://www.kamigami.org
翻译:草泥马 西西   校对:西西   后期:时末
Today is another busy day for the ghost of
Hayama Kimihiko, as he dispenses advice without a care.
タリスマン·サルーンは相変わらず千客万来
Not only is he not running or hiding,
葉山公彦の幽霊は今日ものうのうと人生相談に大忙しと
逃げも隠れもしないどころか
he's even been talking about what happened in Club Exoset.
クラブエグゾゼの件 ネタにしてるありさまですよ
More to the point, just what is his game here?
そもそも こいつは何がしたいんだ
Was his goal to make it look like Hayama Kimihiko was still alive?
葉山公彦が生きているように見せ掛けるのが目的なのか
Then there's no way he'd leave
Hayama's bank account untouched
だったら 銀行口座や外出記録を２カ月ほっとくわけがないでしょ
and his apartment empty for two months, right?
I wonder if his goal really was simply to gain control of Hayama's Avatar.
やっぱり アバターをのっとるのだけが目的なんすかね
I could see someone who commits crimes for kicks doing that, but...
愉快犯と考えればあり得るが
Would someone like that kill?
そのために殺人まで犯すか
Gino, don't try to understand the minds of criminals.
ギノ　犯罪者の心理を理解しようとするな
You'll be taken in.
のみ込まれるぞ
フンッ　それは貴様自身に対する戒めか　狡噛
Was that warning directed at me or yourself, Kougami?
Hey...
おい…
Even if this guy's just doing it for kicks, he's no fool.
やつは愉快犯だったとしてもバカじゃない
He anticipated that he'd fall under suspicion.
自分に嫌疑が掛かると予測していた
There's no way he could have cracked the
Holo-Cosplay in the hall unless he'd prepared beforehand.
会場全員のホロコスをクラッキングするなんて
事前の準備がなけりゃ無理な相談だ
If he thinks he can play us like fools, we'll have to teach him a lesson.
こちらをなめて掛かっているなら 思い知らせてやるまでだ
Karanomori, trace Talisman's access routes.
唐之杜　タリスマンのアクセスルートを追跡しろ
We'll find out who he is and capture him this time for sure.
今度こそ身元を突き止めて押さえる
Don't get too worked up, Gino.
熱くなるな　ギノ
He's clearly very confident in his ability to hide his tracks.
やつは逆探知対策に鉄壁の自信を持ってる
That's why he's still hanging around the social networks as if nothing happened.
だからこそ　今でも平然とソーシャルネットに出入りしてるんだ
But what's the point in us sitting around doing nothing?
ここで手をこまねいて何になる
There might be another way to get a lead on him.
別の方法でやつの尻尾をつかめるかもしれない
There's one more thing that I want to look into.
まだ一つ　気になる件がある
That's fine. Suit yourself.
いいだろう　好きにしろ
I'm still going to trace his access routes.
俺は俺で　逆探知の線で進める
I don't really get stuff like Avatars and virtual worlds.
こういうアバターとかバーチャルとか
俺にはいまいち理解できん
I mean after all, it's our bodies that
actually breathe, sweat, and eat, right?
息をして汗をかいて 飯を食うのは結局この体だろう
Masaoka, I think people like you are an endangered species.
征陸さんみたいな人　今では絶滅危惧種だと思いますよ
Isn't using the net just like using knives for
cooking or using paper to write things down?
ネットって物を調理するための刃物とか 記録するための紙とか
そういうレベルのものじゃないですかね
It's not intrisically good or bad.
いい　悪いじゃない
It's just there, so we accept it and use it.
そこにあるんだから受け入れる 「使う」っていう…
You're good at explaining things, aren't you? Like a teacher.
さすがに 説明がうまいな
教師みたいだ
Really?
そうですか
Have you heard of Rousseau?
ルソーって知ってるか
Um... You mean the philosopher?
えっと…　哲学者の
Yeah. And his work "A Discourse on Inequality".
そう その著作の『人類不平等起源論』
Hold on a second, please. I'll look it up.
ちょっと待ってください 検索してみるんで
You don't need to.
その必要はない
It's all stored right here.
俺の脳内には記憶されてる
Let's say there are two hunters in a forest.
例えば ２人のハンターが森にいる
Should they hunt for rabbits separately?
それぞれ別々にウサギを狩るのか
Or...
それとも
Should they work together and go after bigger prey?
２人で協力して大物を狙うか
Which do you think is the better option?
どちらが正しい判断だと思う
The latter, of course.
もちろん後者です
That's a basic rule of game theory.
ゲーム理論の基本
You work together to catch bigger prey.
協力して大物
That's right. Humans are social by nature.
そのとおり それが人間の社会性だ
Languages, letters, currencies, telephones...
言葉　手紙　通貨　電話
All the communication tools that exist in the
world are there in order to strengthen social nature.
この世に存在するありとあらゆるコミュニケーションツールは全て
この社会性を強化するためのものだ
Do you think the net has the same effect, missy?
ネットにその効果あると思うか　お嬢ちゃん
Yes... I think it does.
ある…　と思います
I see... That sounds kinda interesting.
「ふーん　何だか面白そう」
Shall I give you a bit of assistance?
「ちょっと協力してあげようか」
What?
It wouldn't be a bad idea to get one of the
Public Safety Bureau's rising stars in my debt, right?
「公安局の幹部候補に恩を売っておくのも悪くないじゃない」
It wouldn't be a bad idea to get one of the
Public Safety Bureau's rising stars in my debt, right?
「ふーん　何だか面白そう」
「ちょっと協力してあげようか」
If "sorry" was enough, then we
wouldn't need the police, would we?
「ごめんで済んだら警察はいらないんじゃない」
「あーあ…本当に警察なんかと手を組むんじゃなかった」
I never should have cooperated with the police in the first place.
That's it.
こいつだ
Huh? What are you talking about?
何がですか
I never should have cooperated with the police in the first place.
本当に警察なんかと手を組むんじゃなかった
Her choice of words is different.
言葉遣いが違う
Earlier, she used "Public Safety Bureau". Now, "police".
最初は「公安局」 次は「警察」
You don't think it's just a coincidence?
偶然じゃないですか
Then let's check all the logs available.
じゃ　手に入る限りの過去ログを洗ってみよう
Public Safety
Public Safety Bureau
Just as I thought.
やっぱりだ
Spooky Boogie rarely used the word "police" in the past.
スプーキーブーギーは
過去ログでは「警察」という言葉はほとんど使ったことがない
The one you talked to this morning is a different person.
けさお前が話したのは別人だ
The person we're after now is a murderer
who kills people and takes control of their Avatars.
今俺たちが追っているのは他人のアバターをのっとって成り済ます 殺人犯だ
Our trace showed that the culprit was
operating the Talisman Avatar from here.
逆探では 犯人はここからタリスマンのアバターを操作していた
This apartment.
この部屋だ
Electromagnetic Shield in Operation
Unable to Perform Interior Scan
Door breach.
ドアブリーチ
Huh?
Oh shit!
ヤッベ
If you're calling me, I'm guessing it's bad news.
お前から電話がかかってくるのは悪い兆候だ
Sorry about that. Some hunting dogs got caught in the trap.
そりゃ申し訳ない
猟犬がわなに引っ掛かりましたよ
About time.
とうとうか
I can get you as many replacement proxy servers as
you require, but do you still plan to continue with this?
代わりのプロクシサーバーはいくらでも用意しますけど
まだ続けなさるんで
Of course. It is my duty.
当然だ 俺にはその義務がある
Well, you are Makishima's favorite.
まっあんたは槙島さんのごひいきですからね
Please don't screw up. Seriously.
うまくやってくださいよ　ホントに
How did you guys get out without even a scratch?
何でお前らは無傷なんだ
Hey, don't glare at us like that.
いや　そんなにらまれても…
Maybe somebody here's been misbehaving lately.
日ごろの行いじゃないですか
What is it?
どうした
We've got another victim.
また１人ガイ者が出た
It's Spooky Boogie.
例のスプーキーブーギーだ
We did a search on people who were in Inspector Tsunemori's class
常守監視官の同期生をさらに アフィリエイト収入で絞り込んで突き止めた
and narrowed it down to those who had affiliate income.
Sugawara Shouko, twenty years old.
菅原昭子　二十歳
The murder took place in her home
and was carried out exactly like Hayama's.
現場の自宅は葉山のときとまったく一緒だ
We found pieces of her body in the sewer and
yet her Avatar is still wandering about on the net.
下水管から遺体の断片
なのにアバターだけが ネットをうろつき回ってる
The estimated time of death is before dawn.
死亡推定時刻は今日未明
She must've gotten killed after last night's raid on Exoset.
昨日のエグゾゼの出入りの後やられたな
Let's go back to the office and rework our strategy with Karanomori.
戻って唐之杜と捜査の方針を立て直す
If this keeps up, we'll be playing right into his hands.
このままじゃ　やつの手のひらで踊らされるだけだ
Dammit!
くそっ
Because of me...
私のせいで 彼女を巻き込んでしまって…
she got dragged into this.
Missy...
お嬢ちゃん…
It was my fault.
私が悪いんです
It's all because of me.
私のせいで…
Did you view Spooky Boogie...
お前は スプーキーブーギーを 菅原昭子をおとりにしたのか
Sugawara Shouko... as a decoy?
No...
いえ…
Did you force her to cooperate?
協力を強制した
No...
いえ…
Did you leak information on her to the enemy?
彼女の情報を敵にもらした
No...
いえ…
Then how is this your fault?
じゃあ お前の落ち度はどこにある
But...
それは…
She actually got...
でも　現に彼女は…
Yeah. If we had caught the culprit last night,
ああ　ゆうべの時点で犯人を捕まえていたら
Sugawara Shouko wouldn't have had to die.
菅原昭子は死なずに済んだ
The responsibility for that lies with all of us.
俺たち全員の落ち度だ
For now, just think about fulfilling your responsibilities.
今はただ 責任を果たすことだけを考えろ
Let's catch this guy.
犯人を追うぞ
In short, that's the only thing we can
do to allow the victims to rest in peace.
つまるところ　ホトケの供養にはそれしかないんだよな
I found another weird case.
また１件 妙なのが見つかったよ
Melancholia's Rainy Blue.
メランコリア·レイニーブルー
It belongs to an eighty-two year old man,
８２歳のじいさんのものだったけど
but his grandson begged him to let him use his name and info.
聞けば孫に頼み込まれて 名義だけ貸してたみたい
And then, his grandson died in an accident half a year ago.
で　この孫が実は半年前に事故死してるんだって
Tokitou Yuichi. He was fourteen years old.
時任雄一くん　１４歳
But his Avatar, Melancholia, is still active even after his death.
ところが　彼のメランコリアは彼の死後も活動を続けてる
His grandfather doesn't even know how to access social networks.
祖父はソーシャルネットのアクセス方法すら分からず
In fact, he thought the affiliate income was his pension.
アフィリエイトの入金も年金と勘違いしていたありさまだった
Rainy Blue is a big community, too.
レイニーブルーもすごい大手です
More and more ghost Avatars keep cropping up...
増える増える　幽霊アバター
Is it even possible to operate
several different Avatars at the same time?
別々のアバターを同時に幾つも操るなんて可能なのか
It's not uncommon for heavy users, right?
ヘビーユーザーなら珍しいことじゃないわよね
Yes.
The unusual part is the acting abilities of this culprit.
むしろ異常なのはこの犯人の演技力です
Not only do these hijacked Avatars manage to avoid suspicion,
のっとられたアバター どれも怪しまれるどころか
they're more popular than when their real owners operated them.
かえって本物だったころよりも人気者になってるんですよ
How is it that among tens of thousands
of users, nobody noticed they were fake?
何千人何万人というユーザーが なぜ偽物に気付かない
Because it's not a matter of real or fake.
本物も偽物もないからさ
These Avatars are idols on the net. In other words, icons.
こいつらはネットのアイドル　偶像だ
Icons cannot exist solely through their own will.
偶像ってのは本人の意思だけでは成立しない
Neither Hayama nor Sugawara built their reputations on their own.
葉山も菅原も自分の力だけで地位を築いたわけじゃない
They were able to become Talisman
and Spooky Boogie because their fans
周囲のファンの幻想によって祭り上げられることにより
idolized them based on their own distorted perceptions.
タリスマンやスプーキーブーギーになることができた
The true feelings and natures of these idols are
not the same as the ideals their characters represent.
アイドルの本音や正体と
そのキャラクターとしての理想像とはイコールじゃない
So it's not surprising that a fan could do a better job
than the real owners of playing the idol fans expect to see.
本人よりむしろファンの方が
アイドルに期待されるロールプレイをよりうまく実演できたとしても
不思議じゃない
Are you saying that the culprit is one of their fans?
犯人はこいつらのファンだと
Melancholia, Talisman, and Spooky Boogie.
メランコリア　タリスマン　スプーキーブーギー
He knows those three characters very well,
to the point of being able to imitate them perfectly.
この３つのキャラクターを完全に熟知し模倣することができた
The real culprit is someone whose
level of activity matches that enthusiasm.
それだけ熱を込めてファン活動をしていたやつが
本ボシだ
And how can we find this person?
それをどう見分ける
Just how many people do you
think would be fans of all three Avatars?
３つのアバターに共通するファンというだけで
いったい何人いると思ってるんだ
We can use certain criteria to narrow things down.
絞り込む条件はある
First, Talisman.
まずタリスマンだ
Let's take the top one hundred fans
among the regulars in his CommuField
彼のコミュフィールドの常連のうち
上位１００人について １日当たりの滞在時間をグラフにしてくれ
and draw a graph of their time spent there per day,
predominantly around the estimated time of Hayama Kimihiko's death.
葉山公彦の死亡推定時刻を重点的に
Looks like the time his guests spent there went down overall.
この辺のゲストのフィールド滞在時間
何か軒並み落ち込んでるね
That's around when Talisman's reputation went into decline.
タリスマンの評判が下落した時期ですからね
But after that day, two months ago, it started to recover.
それが２カ月前のこの日を境にして持ち直す
At that point, Hayama was killed and
Talisman was hijacked by an unknown party.
ここで葉山が殺され　タリスマンが誰かに奪われた
And yet, there are some regulars who
stopped coming to Talisman Saloon at that point.
逆にこの時点でタリスマン·サルーンへの来場が途絶えた常連が何人かいる
This pattern on the graph is the key.
このグラフのパターンが鍵だ
When Tokitou Yuichi, who operated Melancholia, died half a year ago,
メランコリアの時任雄一が死んだ半年前
and when Sugawara Shouko,
Spooky Boogie, died the day before yesterday,
そしてスプーキーブーギーの菅原昭子が死んだ一昨日
there should be a user who showed the same pattern.
それと同じパターンを示したユーザーがいるはずだ
I see. That's the culprit's own Avatar.
そうか  それが犯人の本来のアバター
That's right.
そういうことだ
Once the culprit had hijacked the victims' Avatars,
犯人は被害者のアバターをのっとった時点で
he no longer had to visit their CommuFields as a guest.
それぞれが運営するコミュフィールドをゲストとして訪れる必要がなくなった
Well? Does anyone fit these criteria?
どうだ　該当者はいるか
There's only one person who does.
ドンピシャのやつが１人だけ
Midou Masatake, twenty-seven years old.
御堂将剛　２７歳
He works at a virtual sports management company.
バーチャルスポーツ運営会社に勤務
His last Psycho-Pass Hue Check was
run four years ago at an annual checkup.
サイコパス色相チェックは４年前の定期健診が最後
And he hasn't even run into any street scanners since then?
以後は街頭スキャナーに引っ掛かったことすらないのか
Each day, he'd take routes that
would allow him to avoid street scanners.
日ごろからスキャナーの設置場所を避けて通る工夫をするぐらいには
That means he's got something to hide, huh?
後ろ暗い事情があるってことですね
Trace his access records.
こいつのアクセス記録を追跡
Way ahead of you.
もう済ませたわ
His last access was just a few minutes ago
from a budget hotel in Roppongi, Minato ward.
最後のアクセスはほんの数分前
港区六本木のビジネスホテルから
His home address is...
自宅は同じく港区元麻布
located in Motoazabu, also in Minato ward.
Inspector Tsunemori, go investigate this hotel room with Kougami and Masaoka.
常守監視官　狡噛と征陸を連れてホテルの部屋を調査だ
Okay!
はい
I'll go to Motoazubu to investigate
his home with Kagari and Kunizuka.
俺は縢と六合塚とで元麻布の自宅を当たる
He's a dangerous character, skilled at cracking and explosives alike.
相手はクラッキング技術だけでなく
爆発物まで使いこなす危険なやつだ
Don't let your guard down.
気を引き締めて行け
What's that for?
何でそれを
Strong alcohol is the best thing for handling illegal Holograms.
違法ホログラムの対策には強い酒が一番なのさ
That's a trick you can take advantage of after you turn twenty.
二十歳になってからの豆知識だな
Public Safety Bureau! Midou Masatake,
公安局です！
御堂将剛 サイコパスの提示を要求します
please present your Psycho-Pass immediately!
Please come out!
出てきてください
What's going on?
これって…
Forget cracking Holo-Cosplay! He can even crack interior Holo!
ホロコスどころか　内装ホロまでクラッキングしてやがる
Ko!
コウ
Wh-What do we do?
ど…どうすれば
Ko!
コウ
Crime Cofficient is 335.
「犯罪係数　３３５」
Enforcement mode is Lethal Eliminator.
「執行モード　リーサル·エリミネーター」
A pain-inhibiting drug, huh?
痛覚遮断ドラッグか
He won't get far with those injuries.
あのケガなら逃げ切れない
Let's leave the rest to Ginoza and the others.
あとは宜野座たちに任せよう
Welcome back, Midou!
おかえりなさい　御堂君
Welcome back!
おかえり
Yeah...
I'm home.
ただいま
I'm okay.
僕なら平気だ
You guys are eternal.
君たちは永遠の存在なんだ
You were released from the chains of a
physical body and polished by collective intelligence.
肉体の縛りから解放され
集合知によって磨き上げられた
You're the souls most close to Plato's "idea".
最もイデアに近い魂なんだ
No one can look down on you.
誰にも君たちをおとしめることなどできない
I won't let anyone destroy your nobility.
君たちの尊さを壊したりはさせない
I will...
僕が…
I will protect it at any cost.
僕が　必ず守るから…
Thank you.
ありがとう
Thank you, Midou.
ありがとう　御堂君
Once I was guided by you.
かつて君たちに導かれた僕が
And now, together with you, I will guide people and the world.
これからは君たちと共に
人々を…世界を導いていく
You are eternal.
君たちは永遠だ
But...
でもね　もうちょっとうまくできなかったかな
Couldn't you have done a better job, Midou?
御堂君　ねえ
Wait a sec. What on earth...
ちょっと 待って　いったい…
There's something that I've been
searching for. Something I want to know.
僕はずっと探している
知りたいことがあるんだ
I've done whatever it takes to get closer to that goal.
そのためにはどんなことでもやってきた
Say, have you read Terayama Shuuji?
ねえ君　寺山修司を読んだことは
Huh? T-Terayama?
て…　寺山
You should read his play, "Saraba, eiga yo".
読むといい　戯曲『さらば、映画よ』
It seems like everyone is an agent for someone.
みんな誰かの代理人なんだそうだ
And what's more, those agents have
their Avatars communicate in place of them.
代理人たちがさらにアバターを使って コミュニケーションを代理させている
Are you... Makishima?
あんた　槙島…
You have a thorough knowledge of various
Avatars and are able to imitate them perfectly.
あらゆるアバターの個性を熟知し
完全に模倣する
You can become anyone, so I was very
interested in what your personality was like.
何者にも成り得る君の個性とはどのようなものなのか
僕はとても興味があった
That is why I lent you my people and my assistance.
だから人を貸した
力を貸した
S-Stop it!
あっ…や…やめろ
Give them back to me!
返せ　その声でしゃべるな
Don't speak with their voices!
But...
でもね…
I see this play is drawing to a close.
そろそろ底が見えてきた
Now that we've arrived at the final act,
最後の幕引きくらい
instead of borrowing the ideas of others, why don't you come up with an idea of your own to close the curtain?
借り物ではなく君ならではの趣向を凝らしてみてはどうだろう
You bastard... What are you...
貴様　何を…
You can play any character, and yet in the
end it turned out that you yourself are nobody.
何者としても振る舞うことのできる君自身が結局のところは何者でもなかった
Your core personality is null. It's empty.
君の核となる個性は無だ　空っぽだ
You don't have a face of your own.
君には君としての顔がない
That's how you could wear any mask at all over
your smooth, featureless face and have it fit perfectly.
のっぺらぼうだからこそ
どのような仮面でもかぶることができたというだけだ
Shut up! Stop it!
うるさい
黙れ
It's time to say goodbye, Midou Masatake.
そろそろお別れだ　御堂将剛
The hunting dogs, those harbingers of death, have arrived.
死を運ぶ猟犬たちのお出ましだ
Enforcement mode is Lethal Eliminator.
「執行モード　リーサル·エリミネーター」
Aim carefully and eliminate the target.
「慎重に照準を定め　対象を排除してください」
Clear.
クリア
No one else is here... right?
誰もいねえ…よな～？
Then who on earth was he talking to?
いったい誰と話してたんだ
You did quite well this time.
今回 君はじゅうぶんよくやった
In the end, it was Kougami who identified the culprit.
結局　犯人を突き止めたのは狡噛さんでした
I can't believe he was able to understand how the
culprit thought and predict his behavior so accurately.
あんなふうに 犯人の思考を把握し予想するなんて…
That's what Enforcers do.
それが執行官だ
They can understand criminals precisely because
they have the same psychological tendency as them.
犯罪者と同じ心理傾向を持っているからこそできることだ
But...
でも…
Kougami comforted me... and encouraged me.
狡噛さんは私のことを慰めてくれました 励ましてくれました
Even if he's a latent criminal,
あの人が潜在犯だとしても
it's hard to think that he has the same
mind as a homicidal maniac like Midou.
御堂みたいな殺人鬼と同じ心の持ち主だなんて 思えません
You're an Inspector. All you have to do is fulfill your duty as one.
監視官は監視官としての役目だけを果たせ
Draw a line between yourself and the Enforcers.
執行官とは一線を引け
Is that an ironclad rule for this job?
それがこの仕事の鉄則 ですか
No. It's my own rule of thumb.
いや　俺の経験則だ
Huh?
I once lost a partner who made a mistake.
かつて俺は過ちを犯した 相棒を失った
I couldn't stop him.
俺には彼を止められなかった
I don't want you to make the same mistake.
君に同じ轍を踏んでほしくない
This is a file from the Personnel Department.
人事課のファイルだ
Destroy it when you're done reading.
目を通したら破棄しろ
Kougami Shinya. Enforcer. Male.
「狡噛慎也　執行官　男性　２８歳」
Twenty-eight years old. Former Inspector.
「元監視官」
Huh?
While investigating an unsolved case,
Public Safety Bureau Special Case 102,
「未解決事件」
「公安局　広域重要指定事件１０２の捜査中
his Crime Coefficient rapidly increased.
犯罪係数が　急激に上昇」
He prioritized the investigation over his own therapy.
「セラピーによる治療よりも 捜査の遂行を優先」
His Crime Coefficient exceeded the
regulation limit and he was demoted to Enforcer.
「犯罪係数が規定値を逸脱し　執行官に降格」
Fearii teeru wa
It seems all fairy tales
Sakki shinda mitai
Are dead
Renga no byoutou de
In a hospital ward of brick stones
Umaku utaenakute
My voice is too coarse to sing
Kiri ni kemuru yoru
Outside in the foggy haze
Ukabe akai tsuki
A red moon glows
Hora mite watashi wo
Look at me
Me wo sorasanai de
Do not avert your gaze
Kuroi tetsu goushi no naka de
Behind black bars
Watashi wa umarete kitanda
I was born
Behind black bars
Kuroi tetsu goushi no naka de
I was born
Watashi wa umarete kitanda
Akui no daishou wo negae
I wish there were a punishment for evil
I was born
Watashi wa umarete kitanda
I wish there were a punishment for evil
Akui no daishou wo negae
Nozomu ga mama ni omae ni
Always I need you
I wish there were a punishment for evil
Akui no daishou wo negae
Always I need you
Nozomu ga mama ni omae ni
Saa ataeyou seigi wo
Now, grant us justice
Always I need you
Nozomu ga mama ni omae ni
Now, grant us justice
Saa ataeyou seigi wo
Kowashite kowasareru mae ni
Before chaos takes us all
Now, grant us justice
Saa ataeyou seigi wo
Before chaos takes us all
Kowashite kowasareru mae ni
Inga no daishou wo harai tomo ni yukou
Pay the price of fate and let us go together,
Before chaos takes us all
Kowashite kowasareru mae ni
Pay the price of fate and let us go together,
Inga no daishou wo harai tomo ni yukou
Namae no nai kaibutsu
Nameless beasts
Pay the price of fate and let us go together,
Inga no daishou wo harai tomo ni yukou
Nameless beasts
Namae no nai kaibutsu
This story is a work of fiction. The names of all individuals and organizations that appear
in this show are fictitious and any similarity to those in existence in the real world is purely coincidental.
This is a world where the mental state and
personal tendencies of humans can be quantified.
While all sorts of inclinations are recorded and policed,
these measured numbers used to judge people's souls are
commonly called "Psycho-Pass".
This is a world where the mental state and
personal tendencies of humans can be quantified.
While all sorts of inclinations are recorded and policed,
these measured numbers used to judge people's souls are
commonly called "Psycho-Pass".